customize.org 2005-12-12

# [Customize.org] Download Skins, Themes, Wallpapers and Icons for Windows from the original skin site!

Customize.org is committed to providing you the opportunity for a positive experience during your visit to our web site, while respecting and striving to protect your on-line privacy. We have adopted this policy to safeguard your personal information and protect its confidentiality. 

Our site may contain links to other sites. We will make every effort to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy. However, we are not responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by organizations sponsoring these other sites. 

Customize.org collects personal information from our visitors on a voluntary basis only. Personal information may include name, location, email address, etc. The individual information we collect is used only to enhance the on-line experience. We do not sell or transmit personal information to other organizations or third parties. 

All personal information you provide to Customize.org is secured on our server with restricted access. We reserve the right to use agents, who are bound by strict confidentiality guidelines, to perform storage and processing functions. Only designated employees or agents who need to carry out legitimate business functions are permitted to view your personal data. Employees or agents who violate this privacy policy are subject to disciplinary actions, up to and including termination. 

Because Customize.org considers the individual information we maintain to be confidential, our policy is to disclose no personal information to third parties unless release is required by law or is pertinent to judicial or government investigations or proceedings. While Customize.org uses its best efforts and current technology to implement this Privacy Policy, it cannot, of course, guarantee that information it seeks to protect will be protected under all circumstances, including those beyond its reasonable control. 

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use ValueAd, DoubleClick, and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click [**here**](http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp). 

To view ValueAd's Privacy Policy, please click [**here**](http://www.valuead.com/privacy.html). 

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser. 

_We reserve the right to change this policy at any time by notifying visitors of the existence of the new privacy policy._

If you would like to contact us for any reason, please email us at [staff@customize.org](mailto:staff@customize.org).
